(Penny:)it all worked out.
(Bernadette:)When you go to Emily's office to
practice, you'll see. It's fine.
(Penny:)Yeah, I hope you're right.
(Amy:)You really went your entire life
(Amy:)without anyone saying
"I hate you" to your face?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Amy:)I'd say it now,
but look at those cheekbones.
(rock music playing)
(Sheldon:)I miss
Stuart's place.
(Sheldon:)All this loud music
and exposed brick.
(Sheldon:)What, is this
a comic book store,
(Sheldon:)or a rave at the third
little pig's house?
Yup, I wish
Stuart would reopen.
(Howard:)I hate this place, too.
(Leonard:)Okay, him I believe
(Leonard:)because he's an 80-year-old man
in a 15-year-old's T-shirt.
(Leonard:)But you're just upset
(Leonard:)about Stuart and your mom
and all their HBOs.
(Howard:)Yes, I am. You know, I can't
even watch Game of Thrones now
(Howard:)without thinking
of mother saying,
"Stuart, which one is Thrones?"